<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jimdab.com</title>
    <description>Welcome to my own little corner of the web where I will continue to try to practice my writing by sharing my thoughts. 
</description>
    <link>http://jimdab.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jimdab.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 02:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 02:12:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 38</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;orange-is-the-new-green&quot;&gt;Orange is the New Green&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tile guy came today. Bright and early, 7 a.m. there he was knocking on the door. Good thing I was up and showered and ready to go for the day already. Did mostly prep work and now we have orange flooring:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1344.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Orange floor&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had no idea what that stuff was or why it was on my floor. So I looked it up. Nice of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.schluter.com/schluter-us/en_US/Membranes/Uncoupling-(DITRA)/Schluter®-DITRA-&amp;amp;-DITRA-XL/p/DITRA&quot;&gt;Schluter&lt;/a&gt; to put their name so prominently on their product.  Here is what they say it is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Schluter®-DITRA is a polyethylene membrane with a grid structure of square cavities, each cut back in a dovetail configuration, and an anchoring fleece laminated to the underside. The anchoring fleece is embedded in thin-set mortar to provide a mechanical bond to the substrate. Tile is installed over DITRA using the thin-bed method in such a way that the mortar becomes mechanically anchored in the square, cutback cavities of the matting. Designed specifically for ceramic tile and dimension stone installations, DITRA serves as an uncoupling layer, waterproofing membrane, and vapor management layer that accommodates moisture from beneath the tile covering. Further, DITRA performs all these functions while still providing adequate support/load distribution for the tile covering. The combination of these four essential functions allows for the successful installation of tile over a wide range of substrates, including plywood/ OSB, concrete, gypsum, heated floors, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there you go. We have a plywood substrate in our kitchen so it seems to make sense use something like that to…oh hell, who am I kidding? I trust they know what they’re doing. I was just curious what that stuff was. I’m convinced by Schluter’s marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, remember this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1266.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Hole in foyer floor&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They started to tear up the floor in the foyer and discovered another layer of tile under the existing tile. They thought they were going to have to jack-hammer up the concrete underneath it all and then decided to just remove the top layer and tile over it. Well, the tile guy fixed that all up too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1350.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fixed hole in foyer floor&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All better now full of nice, new concrete (&lt;em&gt;or whatever that stuff is&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He says tomorrow he’ll be able to tile the entire floor. That’s great news, except that means we have to go spend the night somewhere. Once the tile is laid, we’re supposed to stay off it entirely for at least 24 hours to allow it to set. Otherwise we could break some of the tile. Since the foyer and kitchen completely block off all access to just about all the rest of the house, we’re gonna go get a room for the night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll still try to get some pix before we take off and post something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s it for today. Tune in next time for the further adventures of Jim &amp;amp; Dena’s kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/07/kitchen-remodel-day-38.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/07/kitchen-remodel-day-38.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 37</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;its-not-easy-being-green&quot;&gt;It’s Not Easy Being Green&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m slacking again. Sure there were a couple of days of inaction lately and they’ve been working the last few days but the progress has been somewhat minimal and hard to show off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They basically took this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1327.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Venting in wall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And turned it into this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1335.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Venting drywalled over&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then turned it into this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1342.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wall painted&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The drywallers have been here finishing up the walls and today the painters showed up and painted it all green. That’s going to be the color of the kitchen. Or at least, those parts of the walls you’ll actually be able to see. That wall there you really won’t see much of  because it’ll have cabinets on top and bottom, a range and range hood in the middle (you can see the venting sticking out of the wall there) and a tile backsplash where you’d expect backsplash to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here you’ll see more of the green:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1343.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Dining area in green&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will be the dining area and that green wall is pretty much what you’ll see when this is all finished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still looks like they need to do another coat over the whole room. Then the tile guy is supposed to show up and start laying tile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is beginning to look like a real room for a change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take care all,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/06/kitchen-remodel-day-37.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/06/kitchen-remodel-day-37.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 31</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;drywall-venting--lessons-learned&quot;&gt;Drywall, Venting &amp;amp; Lessons Learned&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m always amazed at what professional plasterers can do. And how quickly they can do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1329.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Plastered drywall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve done my own drywalling and hole-patching over the years. Having kids, and life in general means you have to patch walls on occasion. I get it done, but it always takes me like 47 rounds of spackling, sanding, spackling some more and it end up looking…OK. Occasionally I achieve “good”. But professionals, in one day the get that whole edge cleaned up and looking like a real wall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then look at this. Here is before:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1290.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wall before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now here it is after today:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1328.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wall after&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s almost looking like a real wall. Not bad especially since almost that entire wall will be covered in cabinets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we also had some venting installed. You’d think they’d have done this before they put all the drywall up, but what do I know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1327.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wall after&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think they had scheduling difficulty with the HVAC guy so they kinda had to do that. This is going to be where and how the range hood vents. They ended up having to go down with the venting rather than up like we had wanted them to. They say it’ll be OK. I’m not sure I’m convinced of that, though I’m not sure what else can be done at this point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally a lesson learned that has nothing to do with the remodeling project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re ever out in your backyard smoking some ribs, and you have left-over apple cider and oil you’ve been using to spray on the ribs to keep them moist during smoking, don’t just toss the remaining cider on the lawn. It’s &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; just like water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1326.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wall after&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lesson learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/31/kitchen-remodel-day-31.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/31/kitchen-remodel-day-31.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 30</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;drywalling&quot;&gt;Drywalling&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today the dry wall people came and patched things up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1325.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Some drywall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see they got the left-over wall all covered up. Patched up the holes in the walls and fixed up the ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1324.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;More drywall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And over here is the other side of the opening to the family room. Guess we’ll have a little angle-thing in the corner there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I cheated a bit. I know I said I’d blog every day someone was here doing something. Well, yesterday the electrician was back doing a couple more things. They put in one too many can-lights in the ceiling so he had to come back and remove the wiring for one of them. That was about it. Didn’t seem worth blogging about so I didn’t. Mea culpa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See ya’ next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/30/kitchen-remodel-day-30.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/30/kitchen-remodel-day-30.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 24</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Guess the city of Janesville is satisfied with their work. Yep, that’s all that was done today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1315.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Electriral 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;p.s. I got to help my son change the spark plugs in his car. OK, he did all the work and I stood around and made fun of him. That’s kind of like helping.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/24/kitchen-remodel-day-24.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/24/kitchen-remodel-day-24.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 23</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;electricity-e-lec-tricity&quot;&gt;Electricity, E-lec-tricity&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we got some electrical work done. How about that. Let’s look at a couple of views from the corners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1309.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Electriral 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1311.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Electriral 2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each of those place where there are white wires hanging down out of holes in the ceiling is where can lights are supposed to go. Curiously, the plans called for 9 can lights to go into the ceiling. When I was speaking with Jerry a week or so ago I was questioning the need for 9 new can lights given that we’re supposed to have 3 pendants hanging over the island. He assured me we’d figure all that out when the electrician came and he’d make suggestions and we’d talk about it and I should not worry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I got holes in the ceiling all wired up and I’m not quite sure I want them that way. And they never did talk with us about it beforehand. Is this normal for contractors? I also noticed there are only 2 pendants roughed in over the island where there’s supposed to be 3. Guess we have some talking to do. And probably a dreaded &lt;em&gt;change order&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the bright side, I figured out what “nailing plates” are. See these&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1314.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nailing plates&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those are nailing plates. Imagine if you will, people hanging drywall with screws (or perhaps nails). They could easily drive that sucker right into the pipes. Hence, put in a nailing plate and that’ll stop any nails or screws from causing you a much bigger problem. I noticed we got a bunch of those nailed up all over the place where the wiring goes through the joists as well. Of course, if Wisconsin used conduit, they wouldn’t have to put in nailing plates to protect the wiring, but that’s a story for another day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That brings us to the end of day 22. Hope you’ve been enjoying this. See you tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/23/kitchen-remodel-day-23.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/23/kitchen-remodel-day-23.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 22</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1306.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;That's it&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yep. That’s it for today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seriously. They capped a couple of pipes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/22/kitchen-remodel-day-22.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/22/kitchen-remodel-day-22.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 21</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What?!? Day 21! Yeah, I reconsidered my day numbering convention. At first, I was going to go by work-days. They started on Tuesday the first, worked through Friday the 4th, that’s 4 days, but then I counted the following Monday as day 5, not day 7. But now with this lull I realized, who cares about work-days, I want to keep count of how many days I’m without a functioning kitchen! So, &lt;em&gt;this is&lt;/em&gt; Day 21. So there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally got back to work today. Plumber came to remove some old plumbing and put in some new.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1300.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Plumbing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See those nice new pipes sticking up out of the floor? That’s our water for our sink and a drain. How nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See those tape lines on the floor? Dena and I got impatient and taped out where the island was going to go so we could get a better feel for what this will look like when it’s done. We like it so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They also took out that last little bit of wall. Cabinets will be all along that wall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1299.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wall gone&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought about titling this post, “Another day, another change-order”. Any time something new comes up that wasn’t in the original estimate, they file what they call a change-order. It’s essentially a legal addendum to our contract specifying what additional thing we’re going to have to pay for. Some of these have been expected—money for the permits, credit for their &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; having to jack-hammer out the concrete in the foyer. That sort of things. Others not so expected, but I kinda feel like they should have been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take today for instance. We’re going to have another change order because, by code, when they put in new plumbing they also have to put in something called “nailing plates”. Now, if this is something required by code and they knew they were putting in new plumbing, don’t you think they would have known they also had to put in nailing plates and factored that into the estimate? &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; think so. &lt;em&gt;smh&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, it was good to once again see some progress. I’ll keep on blogging as long as they keep on working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/21/kitchen-remodel-day-21.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/21/kitchen-remodel-day-21.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>They Want This to Happen</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Another day, another senseless school shooting, and another round of politicians offering their “thoughts and prayers” while not actually doing anything about the epidemic of gun violence in this country. I’ve reached the point where all I can conclude from this is politicians &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; these shootings to continue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why they want this, I don’t know. I know if they actually wanted to reduce the number of people murdered every year by gun violence, they would take action by passing sensible laws to restrict or otherwise control the flood of arms and ammunition into our society. But they don’t. Hence I can only conclude they don’t want to. They want this violence to continue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know, they talk about second amendment rights and how they can’t do anything, but that’s bullshit plain and simple. We don’t let people in this country buy fully automatic weapons and that’s constitutional. Why not restrict the ownership of other types of weapons as well?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because they don’t want to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We already have laws that prevent certain people from owning guns and those laws are perfectly constitutional. Why not pass more laws expanding who can’t own a gun?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because they don’t want to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They’ll say laws like that don’t actually reduce gun violence but that’s a lie. Reduce the availability of guns and you’ll reduce gun violence. It’s that simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My own congressman, Paul Ryan, is the goddamn Speaker of the House! He sets the legislative agenda for the entire House of Representatives. &lt;em&gt;He&lt;/em&gt; decides which bills come to the floor and which do not. Furthermore, he announced he’s retiring at the end of this term so he has nothing to fear from constituents or doners and yet…he’ll do nothing. All I can conclude is that he, like all the other politicians in congress, for some sick reason, &lt;em&gt;wants&lt;/em&gt; this senseless slaughter of children to continue. I don’t understand it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t care what party any of these people belong to, they’re all at fault because they all clearly want this to continue. If they didn’t, they’d do something about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; that simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/thoughts/2018/05/18/another-day-another-shooting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/thoughts/2018/05/18/another-day-another-shooting.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>thoughts</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 6</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, today we got some good news and some bad news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The good news:&lt;/strong&gt; Got a call from the lead guy, Jerry, telling me things are going great. They got the inspection from the city today and all is well. They are happy with all the structural work and things can move ahead. Even better, the workers are ahead of schedule even, &lt;em&gt;way&lt;/em&gt; ahead of schedule. Things are great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The bad news:&lt;/strong&gt; According to the schedule, the next step is to have the electrician and plumber come in and do the work they need to do. But, since we’re &lt;em&gt;way&lt;/em&gt; ahead of schedule, they aren’t ready to be here until week after next. So…a bit of a “lull” in the project. If they can get the folks to come out sooner, great, but usually they’re pretty booked up so…be patient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;sigh&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take care all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/08/kitchen-remodel-day-6.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/08/kitchen-remodel-day-6.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
