<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jimdab.com</title>
    <description>Welcome to my own little corner of the web where I will continue to try to practice my writing by sharing my thoughts. 
</description>
    <link>http://jimdab.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jimdab.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 02:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 02:56:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 72</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;im-exhausted&quot;&gt;I’m Exhausted&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Came home today after work to this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1410.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Range hood and backsplash&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking nice. Got the range hood in today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heh, notice that little black spot on the wall next to the duct-work? That’s a hole in the wall. You may recall seeing previous pics where they had the duct coming out of the wall and the wire coming out next to it. When it was there I thought to myself, “Self, I’m not sure the hood duct work is gonna cover that up. Looks mighty far away.” But honestly, with all the times I’ve tried to warn them about things and they’ve brushed me off telling me not to worry about it, I just let it be. And see, they figured it out. They must have, cause it works!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1411.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Range hood lit up&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can’t hear it, but the fan’s running in that picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that was nice to see. It’s always a bit of a surprise to see what’ll be different when I get home. Like I said previously, we aren’t really &lt;strong&gt;on&lt;/strong&gt; schedule, but things are progressing. Next they’re gonna be in tomorrow to grout the backsplash. And no “I am Grout!” jokes this time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1413.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Backsplash close up&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your basic off-white subway tile with a little strip of highlight. Those are a mix of glass and tile. Brings out the same sort of colors in the floor and walls and cabinets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that’s about it.  See ya next time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/07/11/kitchen-remodel-day-72.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/07/11/kitchen-remodel-day-72.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 70</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;ive-plumbed-the-depths&quot;&gt;I’ve Plumbed the Depths&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OK, so I’m getting a bit silly with the titles on these posts. Shoot me. Looks like they found another plumber cause he was here today and got some stuff hooked up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1409.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Plumbing install&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Got the dishwasher hooked up (sort-of) and installed. There’s plumbing for it all there but there’s still no outlet to plug it in. Guess next step is electrical. To the right is our sink and faucet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1408.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sink&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didn’t realize when we bought it that it came with those grids to put on the bottom or that metal thingie to the left. Turns out that can completely span one of the sinks, front to back, and you can use it as a drying rack or dripping rack or something. Those are square rods and the whole thing turns out to be pretty sturdy. And then it rolls up into a little bundle. It’s pretty cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That was really it for today. Still have quite a bit to finish up: painting, tile, electrical. I’m sure it’ll get done but we’re getting pretty tired of this whole process. We just want it done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, one more thing, we did buy some stools today also to go around the eating end. The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amisco.com/en/product/products/swivel-stools/madison_208.aspx?page=607&quot;&gt;Madison Swivel stool from Amisco&lt;/a&gt;. The body is made of metal and will be a rubbed bronze like the handles. The seat will be a dark fabric and the back…well, the middle slat in the back is going to be wood colored the same as the cabinets. Except they don’t make that color so we ordered them unfinished. I’ll have to finish them myself once they come in. They’ll look good there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s all folks. See ya next time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/07/09/kitchen-remodel-day-70.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/07/09/kitchen-remodel-day-70.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 67</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;lien-on-me&quot;&gt;Lien on Me!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heh, so on the third, we got a notice in our mailbox of a certified letter waiting for us that required a signature. It said the sender was Grams &amp;amp; Associates. Well, that sounded interesting. So a quick &lt;a href=&quot;https://duckduckgo.com&quot;&gt;DuckDuckGo&lt;/a&gt; search turns up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dfgrams.com&quot;&gt;David F. Grams &amp;amp; Associates, S.C. Attorneys at Law&lt;/a&gt;. They’re a law firm in Madison specializing in Trusts and Estates and Business Law. Got me interested. So of course, this is now a holiday so I have to wait to be able to go get the letter. Luckily for me, I usually work from home on Fridays so today I was able to run and pick it up. Here’s what it said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1407.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lien letter&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who don’t want to zoom in it says in part:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The undersigned Subcontractor, having contracted with Property Revival LLC, performed, … plumbing work to improve your Property located at … and, as of the date of this Notice, is owed the sum of $725.00 for said work. If payment in full is not received within thirty (30) days … the Subcontractor intends to file a Claim for Lien on your Property.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So me, being the smart-ass I am texts Jerry, the contractor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jim:&lt;/strong&gt; Hey Jerry, got a problem with your plumber?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jerry:&lt;/strong&gt; uh, yeah…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I honestly have no idea what’s going on but I was assured he and his lawyers have the situation well in hand and I don’t have to worry about it. I’m actually not worried. I suspect these kind of spats happen all the time. But it is something to keep an eye on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe next remodeling project I’ll be my own general contractor and avoid all this crap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, absolutely nothing has happened on the house. Plumbing issues aside, I’m sure the holidays messed up scheduling. We’re hopeful folks will be in next week to actually finish this up. We’re getting tired of this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See y’all,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/07/06/kitchen-remodel-day-67.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/07/06/kitchen-remodel-day-67.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 60</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;countertops&quot;&gt;Countertops!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We gots the countertops!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1401.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Vast black slab&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m lying here again. This all happened Friday, but we took off right after work to go see our son at &lt;a href=&quot;https://und.edu&quot;&gt;UND&lt;/a&gt; where he’s off &lt;a href=&quot;http://aviation.und.edu&quot;&gt;learning to become a commercial airline pilot&lt;/a&gt;. He really likes it there–well, not exactly likes it. He loves flying but could really do without the winters. So he likes to spend his summers up there taking flying classes so he can stay ahead in his program and fly lots. We miss him, but he’s off doing what he loves. That’s important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, we left right after work and I didn’t have time to write all this up, so I’ll just back-date this and pretend like this was all posted last Friday. Back to the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently Dena got to hear a bunch of swearing in a foreign language on Friday. The countertops arrived and she got to watch a bunch of hulky, sweaty, swarthy guys with all their muscles rippling carry in this big, honkin’ slab of quartz.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1402.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Another vast black slab&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And a couple smaller pieces, but those don’t count really. She says they were saying a bunch of things she didn’t recognize but she assumes were swear words. Apparently that stuff is heavy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But they seemed to know what they were doing because the got them in place and they look pretty darn good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1403.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;View from family room&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, that faucet’s not attached. I just stuck it there to see what it would look like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re actually pretty happy the snafu of a couple of weeks ago happened–recall, the one where they told us they ran out of countertop material and as a result we wouldn’t get our counters for about a month? After hearing that, Dena went out and looked at some new stuff and picked out a different style that she thought she liked better. Turns out, she was right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1404.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Another view from family room&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new stuff has more of a brown tone to it with flecks of gold-ish rather than the more pure black with streaks of white. We really like how this blends with everything else we got going on in here. It’s coming along.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, (the real today, Monday) they came and finished up the trim. Looks real nice. That guy does a real nice job on the trim. The rest of this week is supposed to be some finish plumbing, painting (they’re gonna re-paint the walls), and then backsplash tiling. So I hope to have more posts as the week wears on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See y’all,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/29/kitchen-remodel-day-60.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/29/kitchen-remodel-day-60.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 59</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;appliances-trim--trees&quot;&gt;Appliances, Trim &amp;amp; Trees&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, today was a busy day. After a couple of weeks of nothing and a bit of stress all of a sudden today the appliances were delivered, they started to put trim in place and we got the tree damage from the other week cleaned up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First came the appliance guys. Well, actually they came second, but the trim guys got here before the trim so they were pretty much just standing around waiting. Then the appliance guys showed up so they get first billing. Besides, the title, “Appliances, Trim and Trees” has a nicer ring to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The appliances showed up. The first question they ask, “Are you ready for them to be installed?” My answer, “Nope.” Lemme explain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See, we had this delay with the countertops, but I was told to schedule the appliance delivery for the 28th anyway. So I did. Well, as this week was approaching, I’m emailing them saying, “Are you &lt;em&gt;sure&lt;/em&gt; they should be delivering the appliances?” My concern was the electrical and plumbing wasn’t done yet so they wouldn’t be able to plug in or hook up the waterline on the fridge. The range was OK, that already had a gas line and an outlet, but I was a wee-bit concerned about the fridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I point this out to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.propertyrevival.net/revival-services/for-current-home-owners/&quot;&gt;Property Revival&lt;/a&gt;, their response was, “Sure, that’s fine. Have them deliver and install it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me says, “How are they going to hook them up?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They say, “It’s fine, have them deliver and install it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me says, “How are they going to hook them up?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They say, “We told you before it’s fine, don’t worry about it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally on Tuesday we had a bit of a heart to heart and all of a sudden they’re saying, “Uh, hmm, we’ll get back to you on that.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So they scrambled and were able to get the electrician to come out Wednesday and hook up the electrical, but the plumber couldn’t make it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forward to today and we decide to let them install them both without the waterline for the fridge. Property Revival will then have to pull it out, install the waterline, and then put it back. &lt;em&gt;People&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that the fun story is over time for some appliance porn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1388.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Refrigerator&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I finally got my &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.subzero-wolf.com/sub-zero&quot;&gt;fridge&lt;/a&gt;. I like that. That’s exactly how I was picturing this looking. And it works!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the &lt;a href=&quot;https://capital-cooking.com&quot;&gt;range&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1391.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Range&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah, it’s not totally in place yet. A little more story. See, turns out the range is a direct wired hookup, no plug, it has to be hard-wired in place and we have a plug there. Also, the gas line coming up from the floor sticks up too high so the plumber will have to shorten it. So the range isn’t exactly in place quite yet, but both of those things should be done tomorrow. Stay tuned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And while all that was going on, the trim showed up and the trim guys got to work. I have to say, they do a really nice job. They put in the cabinets and now they’re finishing up the baseboard and door trim. We like it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1394.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trim&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Professionals. Way better at mitered corners than I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now on to the final topic of this post. Last week, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gazettextra.com/uploaded_photos/storm-knocks-down-trees-on-janesville-s-east-side/image_00633566-ae9c-5823-863c-30bb8df118af.html&quot;&gt;we had some storms come through Janesville&lt;/a&gt;. Not officially a tornado, but as I was driving down one of the main streets to my house after work there was an awful lot of tree damage and crews out. I said to myself, “uh, oh.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got home and the front was fine, but one of the trees in back, not so much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1382.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tree damage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bummer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were finally able to get &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/paulstreeservicellcjanesville/&quot;&gt;Paul’s Tree Service&lt;/a&gt; to come out here and get it cleaned up for us. They did nice work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1390.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tree cleaned up&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that’s the end of my grand adventure for the day! Pretty hectic first thing in the morning, but turned out well overall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, countertops!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/28/kitchen-remodel-day-59.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/28/kitchen-remodel-day-59.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 45</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Finished up putting handles on all things and re-did the island. I guess they think the countertops will be heavy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1375.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cabinets with handles on them&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pretty slow day. I think now we won’t see much change for a while. The countertop guys are supposed to be in tomorrow to make templates so they can go make the countertops and then come put them on. I think there will be more trim work done in the meanwhile. I’ll keep you all updated as things go by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/14/kitchen-remodel-day-45.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/14/kitchen-remodel-day-45.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 44</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;i-got-a-handle-on-this&quot;&gt;I Got a Handle on this!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back to being clever (&lt;em&gt;or so I think&lt;/em&gt;). Looks like cabinet folks spent the day putting some handles on our cabinets. We really like them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1372.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cabinets with handles on them&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here we have our floating shelves. Those too turned out super nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1373.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Floating shelves&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And finally, they have the outline of the table built. Love the legs we picked out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1371.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Island with table apron&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now we’re gonna have our first, change our mind and it’s gonna cost us, moment. We think the island is too short. That there is 9 feet long (or thereabouts). Our intention is for 4 people to sit in this area, one on each side and 2 on the end. That will work with what’s there, but if people are on the sides and the end, we think knees will be bumping. Probably not too bad, but we don’t want to feel cramped. We have the room, so we’re gonna ask them to re-do that portion and lengthen it out to 10 feet. This will give people on the sides plenty of room. Now I get to compose the email to the contractor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s it. That was a nice anniversary present to us. Now we get to go out to dinner. Eating out at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.clarabo.com&quot;&gt;Clara Bo&lt;/a&gt; in Beloit, WI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/13/kitchen-remodel-day-44.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/13/kitchen-remodel-day-44.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 43</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;cabinets-are-in&quot;&gt;Cabinets are in&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah, no clever titles this time. Not feeling it. Got home yesterday and saw cabinets in the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I gotta say, they look nice and this is starting to look like a kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is where the range and range hood will go. We’re going to have white subway tile as a backsplash between the upper and lowers with an  accent strip somewhere along there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1365.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Range wall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the view of the island and the cabinet wall (for lack of a better term. On that wall between the cabinets will be three floating shelves. Sink and dishwasher here up in the front of the picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1366.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Island and cabinet wall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then another view of the kitchen back toward the range. The refrigerator will go in that opening to the right. The cabinets next to that are pull-out pantry-style cabinets. Those will be nice. On this end of the island the countertop will extend out a couple of feet and be our seating area. We’ll have room for one on each side and two on the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1368.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;More island and stuff&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next they have to finish up trim work. Put in a bit more crown molding and then the trim all around things. This was partly why I didn’t write up this post last night. We had to meet with the contractor to discuss what we wanted for trim. That took way longer than expected. With us, we take forever to really decide on things. We usually need time to let ideas settle and percolate through our minds before we’re happy with them. What makes this doubly hard is all the existing woodwork in the foyer and family room don’t really match each other and now we’re adding more stuff that doesn’t quite match any of that. Dena is having a hard time deciding what to do. We know the shape of the trim, just don’t quite know the color yet. I’m sure she’ll come up with something we’ll be happy with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Progress! Next the counter people come in and measure so they can go make our counters. They already warned us that would take about 2 weeks so we should be patient and expect a bit of a lull again in work. So stay tuned and I’ll keep this blog updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/12/kitchen-remodel-day-43.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/12/kitchen-remodel-day-43.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 42</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;i-am-grout&quot;&gt;I am Grout!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1361.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before grout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1362.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Atter grout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think we need to mop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And we have the beginnings of cabinets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1363.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cabinets&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take care,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/11/kitchen-remodel-day-42.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/11/kitchen-remodel-day-42.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 39</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;we-have-the-tile&quot;&gt;We Have the Tile&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I’m really cheating. I’m writing this two days after the date on this post. But it’s not &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; cheating because the work happened 2 days ago and I’m just getting around to writing about it today. Eh, who cares. I’m writing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had tile put in on Friday! Tile guys came, started at the far side of the kitchen and worked their way out the front door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the view from inside the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1358.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kitchen tile&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the view from my office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1354.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Foyer tile&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m gonna blame my iPhone camera but, in person, the colors I see don’t really look like those pics. But that’s OK because I think I’m getting used to the idea that colors in general change constantly over the course of the day. Dena &amp;amp; I have seen this time and again, we pick out some color that’s brown, or blue, or green or whatever. We get it on the wall and say, “Whoa! that’s not the color we thought it was.” And then later in the day when the sun has moved, “Yeah! That’s the color we wanted.” Even in the same room at the same time, one wall will look one color and another, perpendicular wall will look to be a completely different color. It’s strange.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bringing it back to the tile. What we picked out was kind of a granity-green-ish. Now that it’s in, at different times and in different places, it looks more grey or more brown. Go figure. Regardless, we like it a lot. It’s all really starting to come together. Looks good with the walls in both the foyer and the kitchen and will go nicely with the cabinets once they’re in place. Which should happen Monday because the cabinets were delivered Friday as well!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now for the adventure part of this blog post. As many people know, when tile is laid, you have to stay off it for about 24 hours to allow the thinset (mortar) to set properly. Othewise, the tiles will shift or may even break. Given that the foyer and kitchen are central to our house we planned to spend the night in a hotel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I’m sitting here in my office after the guys left waiting for Dena to come home, when I hear a noise like ductwork flexing. We all know that sound from TV with the good-guy crawling through the ducts to get the bad-guy. So I start hearing that sound and I think, “Oh shit”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1358_molly.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Foyer tile&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That little hole &lt;strong&gt;way&lt;/strong&gt; off in the corner of the kitchen is a vent. Of course the vent cover was removed for the tiling and I don’t see Molly (our cat) around anywhere. I’m convinced she went down that vent hole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See, it’s OK for cats to walk on newly laid tile. They aren’t generally heavy enough to affect it, it’s just us fat humans that can’t walk on it. So I think I have a cat stuck in the duct work and we’re supposed to be leaving for the night and all the next day. We can’t leave her to wander around the ducts for a day. She’ll starve!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So Jim rigs up a way to spider-man-it from my office door to the basement door without disturbing too many tiles. I get down there and start moving aside those drop-ceiling tiles we have down there to try to find the duct work to see if I can somehow poke a cat out of there. Then, of course, Dena calls down, “I have Molly!” She was never in there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stupid cat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we went to dinner and stayed in a hotel here in town. Stopped back Saturday morning to feed and check on the cats (no cats in the ducts), spent a nice day with Dena’s mom helping her get some shopping done, got back last night (still not cats in ducts) and could finally walk all over it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the end of our tile adventure. Cabinets were delivered late Friday and should be put in place come Monday. Gonna really start looking like a kitchen now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take care,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/08/kitchen-remodel-day-39.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/06/08/kitchen-remodel-day-39.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
