<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jimdab.com</title>
    <description>Welcome to my own little corner of the web where I will continue to try to practice my writing by sharing my thoughts. 
</description>
    <link>http://jimdab.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jimdab.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 02:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 02:19:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 30</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;drywalling&quot;&gt;Drywalling&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today the dry wall people came and patched things up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1325.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Some drywall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see they got the left-over wall all covered up. Patched up the holes in the walls and fixed up the ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1324.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;More drywall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And over here is the other side of the opening to the family room. Guess we’ll have a little angle-thing in the corner there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I cheated a bit. I know I said I’d blog every day someone was here doing something. Well, yesterday the electrician was back doing a couple more things. They put in one too many can-lights in the ceiling so he had to come back and remove the wiring for one of them. That was about it. Didn’t seem worth blogging about so I didn’t. Mea culpa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See ya’ next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/30/kitchen-remodel-day-30.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/30/kitchen-remodel-day-30.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 24</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Guess the city of Janesville is satisfied with their work. Yep, that’s all that was done today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1315.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Electriral 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;p.s. I got to help my son change the spark plugs in his car. OK, he did all the work and I stood around and made fun of him. That’s kind of like helping.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/24/kitchen-remodel-day-24.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/24/kitchen-remodel-day-24.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 23</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;electricity-e-lec-tricity&quot;&gt;Electricity, E-lec-tricity&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we got some electrical work done. How about that. Let’s look at a couple of views from the corners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1309.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Electriral 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1311.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Electriral 2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each of those place where there are white wires hanging down out of holes in the ceiling is where can lights are supposed to go. Curiously, the plans called for 9 can lights to go into the ceiling. When I was speaking with Jerry a week or so ago I was questioning the need for 9 new can lights given that we’re supposed to have 3 pendants hanging over the island. He assured me we’d figure all that out when the electrician came and he’d make suggestions and we’d talk about it and I should not worry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I got holes in the ceiling all wired up and I’m not quite sure I want them that way. And they never did talk with us about it beforehand. Is this normal for contractors? I also noticed there are only 2 pendants roughed in over the island where there’s supposed to be 3. Guess we have some talking to do. And probably a dreaded &lt;em&gt;change order&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the bright side, I figured out what “nailing plates” are. See these&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1314.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nailing plates&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those are nailing plates. Imagine if you will, people hanging drywall with screws (or perhaps nails). They could easily drive that sucker right into the pipes. Hence, put in a nailing plate and that’ll stop any nails or screws from causing you a much bigger problem. I noticed we got a bunch of those nailed up all over the place where the wiring goes through the joists as well. Of course, if Wisconsin used conduit, they wouldn’t have to put in nailing plates to protect the wiring, but that’s a story for another day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That brings us to the end of day 22. Hope you’ve been enjoying this. See you tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/23/kitchen-remodel-day-23.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/23/kitchen-remodel-day-23.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 22</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1306.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;That's it&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yep. That’s it for today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seriously. They capped a couple of pipes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/22/kitchen-remodel-day-22.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/22/kitchen-remodel-day-22.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 21</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What?!? Day 21! Yeah, I reconsidered my day numbering convention. At first, I was going to go by work-days. They started on Tuesday the first, worked through Friday the 4th, that’s 4 days, but then I counted the following Monday as day 5, not day 7. But now with this lull I realized, who cares about work-days, I want to keep count of how many days I’m without a functioning kitchen! So, &lt;em&gt;this is&lt;/em&gt; Day 21. So there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally got back to work today. Plumber came to remove some old plumbing and put in some new.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1300.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Plumbing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See those nice new pipes sticking up out of the floor? That’s our water for our sink and a drain. How nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See those tape lines on the floor? Dena and I got impatient and taped out where the island was going to go so we could get a better feel for what this will look like when it’s done. We like it so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They also took out that last little bit of wall. Cabinets will be all along that wall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1299.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wall gone&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought about titling this post, “Another day, another change-order”. Any time something new comes up that wasn’t in the original estimate, they file what they call a change-order. It’s essentially a legal addendum to our contract specifying what additional thing we’re going to have to pay for. Some of these have been expected—money for the permits, credit for their &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; having to jack-hammer out the concrete in the foyer. That sort of things. Others not so expected, but I kinda feel like they should have been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take today for instance. We’re going to have another change order because, by code, when they put in new plumbing they also have to put in something called “nailing plates”. Now, if this is something required by code and they knew they were putting in new plumbing, don’t you think they would have known they also had to put in nailing plates and factored that into the estimate? &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; think so. &lt;em&gt;smh&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, it was good to once again see some progress. I’ll keep on blogging as long as they keep on working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/21/kitchen-remodel-day-21.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/21/kitchen-remodel-day-21.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>They Want This to Happen</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Another day, another senseless school shooting, and another round of politicians offering their “thoughts and prayers” while not actually doing anything about the epidemic of gun violence in this country. I’ve reached the point where all I can conclude from this is politicians &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; these shootings to continue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why they want this, I don’t know. I know if they actually wanted to reduce the number of people murdered every year by gun violence, they would take action by passing sensible laws to restrict or otherwise control the flood of arms and ammunition into our society. But they don’t. Hence I can only conclude they don’t want to. They want this violence to continue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know, they talk about second amendment rights and how they can’t do anything, but that’s bullshit plain and simple. We don’t let people in this country buy fully automatic weapons and that’s constitutional. Why not restrict the ownership of other types of weapons as well?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because they don’t want to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We already have laws that prevent certain people from owning guns and those laws are perfectly constitutional. Why not pass more laws expanding who can’t own a gun?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because they don’t want to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They’ll say laws like that don’t actually reduce gun violence but that’s a lie. Reduce the availability of guns and you’ll reduce gun violence. It’s that simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My own congressman, Paul Ryan, is the goddamn Speaker of the House! He sets the legislative agenda for the entire House of Representatives. &lt;em&gt;He&lt;/em&gt; decides which bills come to the floor and which do not. Furthermore, he announced he’s retiring at the end of this term so he has nothing to fear from constituents or doners and yet…he’ll do nothing. All I can conclude is that he, like all the other politicians in congress, for some sick reason, &lt;em&gt;wants&lt;/em&gt; this senseless slaughter of children to continue. I don’t understand it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t care what party any of these people belong to, they’re all at fault because they all clearly want this to continue. If they didn’t, they’d do something about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; that simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/thoughts/2018/05/18/another-day-another-shooting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/thoughts/2018/05/18/another-day-another-shooting.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>thoughts</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 6</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, today we got some good news and some bad news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The good news:&lt;/strong&gt; Got a call from the lead guy, Jerry, telling me things are going great. They got the inspection from the city today and all is well. They are happy with all the structural work and things can move ahead. Even better, the workers are ahead of schedule even, &lt;em&gt;way&lt;/em&gt; ahead of schedule. Things are great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The bad news:&lt;/strong&gt; According to the schedule, the next step is to have the electrician and plumber come in and do the work they need to do. But, since we’re &lt;em&gt;way&lt;/em&gt; ahead of schedule, they aren’t ready to be here until week after next. So…a bit of a “lull” in the project. If they can get the folks to come out sooner, great, but usually they’re pretty booked up so…be patient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;sigh&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take care all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/08/kitchen-remodel-day-6.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/08/kitchen-remodel-day-6.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 5</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;More walls coming down and beams going up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I missed Day 4. That was last Friday. I got home from work that day, took a couple of pics and then headed to the airport to go to Vegas to watch my older brother get married. That was fun, but no time for writing blog posts. So, today is a two-fer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recall, prior to Friday, the kitchen looked like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1272.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Day 3 kitchen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I came home, it looked like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1274.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kitchen without wall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re opening up the wall to the family room to make the whole thing more open. To do that, they built a temp-wall to hold up the ceiling while they removed the old wall and put in a new beam to hold up the second floor. Like such:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1279.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Beam me up Scotty!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and such:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1280.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Beam me up Scotty, again!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That was about it from Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then today I come home and things are looking a bit more open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1291.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;No wall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A big improvement. Our family room is hidden behind that wall of plastic. A good look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then they turned their sights to soffits. Remember, way back when, when the one wall looked like this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1124.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Old buffet wall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, now it looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1290.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;No soffits&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re still gonna put cabinets in that opening. But for that, you’ll have to wait a while. I don’t want there to be any spoilers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take care all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/07/kitchen-remodel-day-5.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/07/kitchen-remodel-day-5.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 3</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;And the walls come tumbling down—well, sort of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1272.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Day 3 kitchen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continue to make slow but steady progress I guess. That whole wall, for the most part, is coming down and will then be open to the family room. Looks like they’ll need to move some plumbing I’m thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then in the foyer they got that top layer of tile off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1271.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Day 3 foyer&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe we should just leave it? Kinda trendy and plaid-looking with the old tile and the left-over grout. OK, maybe not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s it for today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/03/kitchen-remodel-day-3.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/03/kitchen-remodel-day-3.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 2</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m shocked. I honestly think never before in the history of home remodeling projects has a project been reduced in scope and price. But yet, that is exactly what happened to me today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I generally approach this project with the thought that if the project lead ever calls me in the middle of the day, it’s gonna be bad news. Why else would they need to call, right? So today I get a call from Jerry and I’m thinking, “oh shit.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;phone rings&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jim: Hello.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jerry: Hi Jim, this is Jerry, how you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jim: Fine ’til you called. (Yes, I really said that, I know, I’m a jerk.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But then he goes on to tell me that he actually had good news. Remember that tile over tile over concrete thing in the foyer? Well, turns out, he decided if he removed it all the way down, he would have to rebuild up the subfloor by 2–3” which seemed silly to him. So he had the bright idea to only remove the top layer of tile and then tile right back over the old layer. This means no jackhammering, no rebuilding up the subfloor which saves both time and money from the original quote! Yay me! So, all he has to do is fix up that area they already dug into and they’re good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will wonders never cease? Let’s hope so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the rest of the kitchen, they basically got all the tile off. That was about it for the day. I’ll leave you with one glorious picture of a plywood floor and talk to you later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1270.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Day 2 kitchen floor&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/02/kitchen-remodel-day-2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/05/02/kitchen-remodel-day-2.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
