<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jimdab.com</title>
    <description>Welcome to my own little corner of the web where I will continue to try to practice my writing by sharing my thoughts. 
</description>
    <link>http://jimdab.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jimdab.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 13:07:51 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 13:07:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.1.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bears vs. Giants Game Prediction</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m going to wimp out on this one and not actually predict a winner. Allow me to explain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to know this early in the season just what teams are going to be. Especially this season with no training camp and no pre-season, teams are more sloppy and less prepared which makes the prediction business even more difficult than usual. In the case of the Bears and Giants we have two teams both of whom show some inklings of being better at times, while still showing lots of inconsistency and problems they’ve yet to overcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bears should be able to consistently run the ball, but I’m not convinced that will be enough to score many points. Trubisky should be able to take advantage of what’s considered a weak secondary and make some big plays. However, we’ve not yet seen he can do that on a consistent basis so I expect we’ll see him take plenty of shots down field but have a lot of near misses—and some not so near.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the Giants, their QB appears to be improving yet is still turnover-prone and it’s easy to rattle him. If the Bears are able to generate significant pass rush against him they should be able to force turnovers but again they’ve not done that consistently for a while now. The Bears’ defensive front and their middle linebackers need to play much better than they did against the Lions if they hope to stop Saquon Barkley from doing them what Peterson did all too often last week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end, I expect this to be a sloppy, inconsistent game for both teams on both sides of the ball, leaving fans able to find hope for the future while still allowing critics to point to the many flaws they’ve yet to overcome. I predict a final score of 13-10 but I honestly can’t say which team will have the 13 and which the 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Score&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Giants: ?&lt;br /&gt;
Bears: ?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/bears/2020/09/19/bears-v-giants-prediction.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/bears/2020/09/19/bears-v-giants-prediction.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>bears</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bears vs. Lions Post Game</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Wow. Just wow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For three quarters I was spot-on in my prediction for this game. Trubisky looked totally lost and as bad or worse than he had in any game in 2019. Missing wide open receivers, overthrowing, throwing behind. He sucked. Bad. I seriously believed they should bench him at half and bring in Foles, he was that bad. Defense also sucked. The pass rush was virtually non-existent, Mack was having a hard time beating single blockers, Stafford was having his way throwing the ball and AP was gashing them in the running game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, at the end of the 3rd quarter Bears get the ball back and I swear to God I texted my brothers and said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Going totally homer here: OK, now it clicks and Mitch balls out and scores 3 TDS in a row here. Bears win 27-23.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And sure as shit he does that. All of a sudden Trubisky is completing beautiful passes down field and completely took charge of the game. I don’t get it. Had this game ended in a loss, I could easily see them starting Foles next week. As it is, I don’t see how they can &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; start him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As usual, the Bears gave me my full 3 hours of excitement and entertainment. Sometimes utterly heart-breaking other times thrilling. Can’t wait til next week!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/bears/2020/09/13/bears-at-lions-post-game.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/bears/2020/09/13/bears-at-lions-post-game.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>bears</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bears at Lions Game Prediction</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Let’s start this off right from the top: Hate to say it, I don’t see the Bears winning this game. The Bears defense isn’t going to dominate as everyone seems to expect and the offense for the first time in recent years will be stymied by the Lions defense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mitch Trubisky has played some of his best games vs. the Lions. According to most people who know way more about this than me, this is because under head coach Matt Patricia, the Lions tend not to disguise their coverage or use many stunts when rushing the QB. As a result, what Trubisky sees pre-snap is what he encounters after the play starts. However, this is Patricia’s third year with Detroit and the general consensus is if they don’t improve and make the playoffs this year, both he and their General Manager will be out. Accordingly, Detroit brought in a new Defensive Coordinator and, if everyone I’ve read recognizes the reason Trubisky has been so successful against the Lions is because of how they play their defense, I have to believe the Lions know this too and will finally be prepared for him. I expect them to do things on defense designed to confuse Trubisky and he’ll regress to his 2019 self of stupid indecision and leave the offense struggling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the defensive side of the ball for some reason most people I read seem to be discounting the fact that both their edge rushers, Khalil Mack and Robert Quinn are injured with Quinn listed as doubtful. In the first half of last season, Matt Stafford was playing some of the best football of his career before he got injured. Word is this season he’s looking even better and people are expecting him to pick up right where he left off last year. Without Quinn and Mack putting pressure on Stafford, he will have plenty of time to pick apart the Bears defense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the offense struggling and the defense unable to pressure Stafford consistently, I see the Bears struggling and eventually losing this game. I hope I’m wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final score&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Bears 17&lt;br /&gt;
Lions 24&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/bears/2020/09/12/bears-at-lions.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/bears/2020/09/12/bears-at-lions.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>bears</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It is done!!</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;finally&quot;&gt;Finally&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OK, I’ll be honest, it’s been done for a few weeks now, I’m just finally getting around to writing about it. I won’t bore you with all the details of getting the “final” bill only to have items we had to haggle over. I just want to say when your contractor won’t give you credit for unused material they purchased because it’s open and you ask for the material back since you paid for it, and when you get it back from them, you see the “opened” part consists of them having pulled open 1 of the four flaps on the cover, but none of the material is actually used, you know your contractor is trying to screw you over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it’s done. We won’t ever do business with Property Revival again. The final payment was made on September 18, 140 days after the “9 week” project started May 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enough bitching.  As promised, here are some before and after pictures of the whole thing. Sit back and enjoy the carousel. We actually like our kitchen a lot and can’t wait to host our big family Thanksgiving dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/10/06/it-is-done.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/10/06/it-is-done.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bears week 4 - Post game</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;i-finally-get-my-boring-game&quot;&gt;I finally get my boring game&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently said to my wife, I wanted to watch a boring Bears game. By that I meant I wanted to see the Bears score quickly, take charge of the game and cruise to an easy victory with the end never in any doubt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I got that game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could not have been more wrong in my prediction earlier today when I said I doubted Trubisky would make the plays downfield he would need to make to win this game. He made those plays all game long. This is the kind of offensive performance most fans have been hoping the Bears  would have all season and today they delivered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Off to a bye-week and then they go to Miami. I’m excited to see what changes the Bears make and how they perform after the bye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bear down!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/bears/2018/09/30/bears-week-4-post-game.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/bears/2018/09/30/bears-week-4-post-game.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>bears</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bears week 4</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;can-they-move-to-3-1&quot;&gt;Can they move to 3-1?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bears started a somewhat surprising 2-1 this season. Most of that  on the back of the defense which is unsurprising given the addition of Khalil Mack. This week they face another surprisingly good team, the Tampa Bay Buccaneers. Can the Bears beat them and move to 3-1 on the season? I won’t be surprised if they don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far this season, the Bucs back-up quarterback, Ryan Fitzpatrick has been surprisingly good. Over 400 yards passing per game and 11 touchdowns. That’s impressive. From what I’ve read though, he hasn’t  been pressured and he doesn’t do well under pressure. This favors the Bears who have one of the best, if not &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; best, front 7 in the NFL. I expect them to get to Fitzpatrick and force him to make a number of mistakes. That’s the good news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other side, Tampa Bay has a pretty good run defense which will force the Bears to rely on Trubisky to make plays downfield. From what we’ve seen so far, that probably won’t happen. Eventually Trubisky is going to get comfortable in the pocket and make those plays, I’m just not sure that will happen this week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end, I expect the Bears offense will be effectively stymied and the defense will be mostly effective but still have a couple of blown plays resulting in scores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prediction:&lt;/strong&gt; Bears 10, Buccaneers 17&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go Bears!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/bears/2018/09/30/bears-week-4.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/bears/2018/09/30/bears-week-4.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>bears</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 98</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;no-theyre-still-not-done&quot;&gt;No. They’re Still. Not. Done.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re giving up. Coming up on day 100 of the &lt;em&gt;Great Kitchen Remodel&lt;/em&gt; and they &lt;strong&gt;still&lt;/strong&gt; aren’t done. Though I think I’m done blogging about it until they are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It hasn’t been totally silent. Last week Monday they installed the pop-up outlet. That’s pretty cool. Of course, that was the only thing that happened last week. Today they came in a cleaned up a few odds and ends, but that was it. Who knows what else will be done or when it will be done. They don’t really talk to us much any more other than tell us they have to get the plumber back in, they have to get the tile guy back in, they have to get the electrician back in…sigh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, I’m just hoping they’re done by Thanksgiving. But until then, I’m done writing about this fiasco. Next post will be when it’s all done and I hope to have some before and after pics to sum it all up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/08/06/kitchen-remodel-day-98.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/08/06/kitchen-remodel-day-98.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 87</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;putzing-along&quot;&gt;Putzing Along&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been slacking a little bit lately. They’ve been here doing things in bits and pieces. They got the backsplash for the range in place. They cleaned. They got the microwave installed and did some additional electrical stuff (&lt;em&gt;but of course, didn’t install the popup outlet because we’re still lacking a hole&lt;/em&gt;). And I haven’t been blogging any of that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Because we just want them done!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just dragging on way too long and we’re both getting a bit worn out by the whole process. We just want them done and out of our house. The last two days they’ve made some progress by finishing tiling some additional backsplash. This was an extra.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went from this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1400.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1471.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After they got the backsplash on the other wall, Dena was looking around and decided she wanted it continued there in that little opening. So we did it. We’re pretty happy. We think it helps tie the whole room together a bit more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still a few more odds and ends and we still might not have the whole lien thing worked out yet. I’ll check on the status of that tomorrow. I think it’s taken care of but one more call to be sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s it,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/07/25/kitchen-remodel-day-87.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/07/25/kitchen-remodel-day-87.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 82</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;i-got-a-hole-in-one&quot;&gt;I Got a Hole in One!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1429.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture of my holes&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yep. Let’s see, last post was Day 74, this is Day 82. So in 8 days they were able to drill 2 holes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, that’s not entirely accurate. In those intervening 8 days besides drilling 2 holes they did come back and repaint the kitchen (&lt;em&gt;getting paint on the cabinets and trim in the process&lt;/em&gt;) and a cleaning crew came in and cleaned the entire kitchen and foyer. (&lt;em&gt;Why have a cleaning crew come in to clean when there is still some pretty major work to be done? I don’t know.&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But still, progress has been painfully slow lately. We actually have  neighbors coming up to us now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neighbor&lt;/strong&gt; What are you having done?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Us&lt;/strong&gt; The kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neighbor&lt;/strong&gt; That’s it!?!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, we sheepishly admit, that’s it. I get there are delays in any project, but this is getting a bit ridiculous. It’s not like we’ve been asking for a bunch of last-minute changes. They just aren’t very good at scheduling things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh well, the two holes are there to be filled by an air gap for the dishwasher and a switch for the disposal. A little push-button thingie right there in the surface of the countertop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re also having a pop-up outlet installed in the middle of the island. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.lewelectric.com/catalog/pur15-bk/&quot;&gt;This one&lt;/a&gt; in fact. It’ll be a round thing you push down on and it pops up and you got 2 outlets and 2 USB ports to plug things in. When done, push it back down and it’s out of the way. We liked that idea better than hanging cords off the side to plug things in. But, of course, when the guys were here drilling holes for the air gap and the switch, they couldn’t drill the hole for the outlet because they didn’t have the right drill bits with them. So, now they’ll have to come back some time next week and finish that up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The electrician should be here next week as well to install the rest of the electrical stuff. (&lt;em&gt;Except the pop-up outlet of course, he’ll probably have to come back later to finish that up.&lt;/em&gt;) Then that’ll just about wrap it up for major stuff. Then comes the dreaded punch-list. We get to go around and list all the things we see wrong that we want them to come fix (&lt;em&gt;like finish installing the range for example&lt;/em&gt;) and then wait for them to come fix it. At this rate, we’re honestly wondering if we’ll have our kitchen done by Thanksgiving. Which we’d better cause we’ll be having our families over just like we do every year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But in the meanwhile, we’ve actually started to use it all a little bit. Last Sunday we roasted a chicken in the oven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See, when I was busy analyzing every aspect of kitchen ranges trying to pick out the one I wanted (&lt;em&gt;no, I’m not obsessive about these things, just a bit picky&lt;/em&gt;) the Capital range was high on the list but it came with this rotisserie. My thought at that time was, “When are we ever going to use a rotisserie?” But, in the end I liked that one the most so we got it—even if I thought I’d never actually use that giant metal fork thingie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flash forward to last sunday and we say, “Hey, let’s roast a chicken!” So we do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1422.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chicken roasting&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Comes with that massive metal rod which has a place way in the back corner for you to stick it. After, of course, you impaled your meat on it. Then you just turn it on and let the rotisserie magic happen (&lt;em&gt;and put a pan underneath it otherwise you’ll have a huge mess all over the bottom of your oven&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hour or so later and, damn, that came out looking good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1423.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chicken roasted&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we carved it up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1424.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chicken cut up&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And ate it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1425.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chicken dinner&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those beans are from our garden. The bird was stuffed with lots and lots of herbs from our herb garden as well. We were both surprised at just how juicy and flavorful it was. We could actually taste all the fresh basil, oregano and thyme I stuffed in there. It was amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So guess what, we’ll be using the rotisserie again. I’m glad we got it. Oooh, maybe I’ll rotisserie the turkey for Thanksgiving!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that’s the end of my story for today. Hope you’ll join me all next time on&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Adventures of Jim &amp;amp; Dena’s Kitchen&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or is it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jim &amp;amp; Dena’s Kitchen Nightmare!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eh, whatever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take care,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/07/21/kitchen-remodel-day-82.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/07/21/kitchen-remodel-day-82.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kitchen Remodel Day 74</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;let-there-be-light&quot;&gt;Let there be light!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And there was light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1416.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;money-shot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There it is. I think we’re entering the final stretch. Electrician was here and he put in all the outlets, switches and ceiling lights. Makes a real difference. Looking almost done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a closer-up shot of the actual lights over the island. Dena has a really good eye for that sort of thing. She picks well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1418.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pendant light&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And we got flames too! Check this out. Six full burners of bright blue flames. Not sure I’ll ever cook six things at once, but you never know. Thanksgivings get mighty crowded around here sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jimdab.com/img/IMG_1417.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Flames!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back Monday to paint, and tile, and fix the one pantry cabinet, and finish up some plumbing and finish up some electrical. Yeah, right. That’s the plan at least. Seems a bit unrealistic to me given how pokey this whole thing has been. But, we’ll see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until then, we may actually cook something on our new range this weekend. I’ll let you know if we do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take care,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIm&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/07/13/kitchen-remodel-day-74.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jimdab.com/kitchen/2018/07/13/kitchen-remodel-day-74.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>kitchen</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
